misssixty.com 2014-12-31

# MissSixty

This Privacy Policy applies to the use of this website (www.misssixty.com, the "Website") operated by E-volve Service Sagl and the use of all services offered by the Website. It is our aim to ensure the protection of your personal information at any time. We kindly ask you to carefully read this Privacy Policy to learn which information is collected and for what purposes we use the collected information. 

* ### 1 Types of information we collect

When you sign up for an user account at the Website, we ask you for personal information, such as first and family name, address, country of residence, gend-er, date of birth, nationality, email address, telephone number, credit card details. In addition, you are requested to choose an username and a password for your user account. 

When you are buying a product from the Website or when you are using other services offered by the Website, we collect transaction information, such as what kind of products you bought, delivery address, credit card and payment details. 

When you communicate with us, for example by sending e-mails, we retain such communication in order to process your enquiries, respond to your requests and to improve our services. 

In addition, we collect information, such as your IP-address, browser type and version, operating system and platform, automatically whenever you interact with us. On the Website, we use so called "cookies" and we collect the before mentioned information whenever your web browser accesses the Website. Coo-kies are some kind of data which we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser in order to help us to recognize you when you access the Website, to remember your settings and to personalize the Website according to your needs. You may disable cookies in the settings of your web browser but please be aware that you may not use all of the services of the Website if cookies are disabled. 

* ### 2 How we use the collected information

All information that we collect from our customers help us personalize and im-prove your shopping experience at the Website. The information we collect is used to handle orders, deliver requested products and services, personalize content and shopping experiences on the Website, process payments, optimize our services, products and the Website. Since we want our customers to feel safe, we also use the collected information to detect, investigate and prevent fraud and other illegal activities. In addition, we use the information to provide you with special offers and information about products that might be of interest to you. 

We retain your personal information only for as long as we have a legitimate business purpose or for as long as we are required by law. After this period, we will delete all of your personal information. 

* ### 3 Sharing of information with third parties

Protecting your personal information is really important to us and we want you to be certain that your personal information is in good hands. We share your infor-mation only as described below and with third parties that follow the applicable data protection laws and that ensure an adequate level of protection with respect to your personal information. We will share your personal information with Sixty s.p.a..Sixty s.p.a. is contractually obliged to comply with applicable data protection laws and your personal information will therefore be properly protected at all times. 

For certain services, such as the delivery of your products, the processing of your payment, customer support, we engage third parties. These third parties will have access to those personal information we collected from you that is necessary in order for them to perform their functions. They are not allowed to use your personal information for any other purpose and they are contractually obliged to comply with applicable data protection laws. 

We will release personal information in case we are required by law, for enforcing our General Terms and Conditions and other agreements and in case of detection, investigation and prevention of fraud and other illegal activities. 

In all other cases, we share your personal information with third parties only if we have your explicit consent. You will have the opportunity to choose not to share any personal information with any third party. If and when we transfer your personal information to a third party domiciled outside, we will ensure that your personal information is protected by adequate safeguards. 

* ### 4 Security of your personal information

In order to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, disclo-sure and modification, we have implemented technical and other security meas-ures. We adapt these security measures from time to time and try to provide a high level of security at all times. Nevertheless, you have to be aware that, de-spite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. In addi-tion and in order to help us to maintain a high level of security, we kindly ask you to keep your username and password confidential and not to disclose it to third parties. 

Some of your information will be stored on a server provided by a third party, currently on a server of Amazon Web Services based in Ireland. We have chosen this third party provider based on our best knowledge and we might change the third party provider from time to time, especially if we are of the opinion that your personal information is no longer protected accordingly. Such third party provider is always endeavoring to provide for a high security standard. However, we cannot take responsibility for this third party provider's actions.

* ### 5 Your information rights

You can contact us anytime and request that we inform you about all personal information that we have collected and stored about you. In addition, you may request that we correct, amend or delete such personal information. Please note, that if you request us to delete your personal information, we will no longer be able to provide you with our services. 

By accessing your account on the Website, you have at any time the possibility to correct, amend or delete your personal information such as your first name, your family name, your address, your country of residence, your credit card details. Of course, you may delete your account at any time.

* ### 6 Controllers of personal information and contact

Your personal information will be controlled by E-volve Service Sagl. If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, the handling of your personal data or would like to exercise your information rights, please contact:

E-volve Service Sagl - Via Cantonale 2b - 6928 Manno - CH 

We take your concerns seriously and we will try to resolve any issue relating your personal information for you as soon as possible.

* ### 7\. Changes to this Privay Policy

Please note, that we may change this Privacy Policy from time to time in order to better protect your personal information. We recommend that you regularly check this Privacy Policy when you access your account. Your continued use of the Website indicates your agreement to the new Privacy Policy. 

* ### 8 Related information

Before using the Website, we kindly ask you to also carefully read the following documents: 

  * General Terms and Conditions 

E-volve Service Sagl
